Jesús Ruiz

Full Stack Developer and Graphic Designer

I am a Junior Full Stack Developer with 2 years of experience in PHP and Laravel, and basic knowledge of frontend technologies such as JavaScript, React, Astro and NextJS. I have experience in deploying applications on various platforms, which allows me to manage projects comprehensively.

In addition, I have 6 years of experience as a Senior Graphic Designer, specialized in Visual Identity. This combination of skills allows me to contribute in all phases of the project: from the design of visual prototypes, through backend and frontend development, to deployment and maintenance.

- +51 935 035 069 jesuizmail@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/jesuiz github.com/Jesuiz
- △ Visit my portfolio: jesus-portfolio.vercel.app
- ⊕ I currently reside in Lima, Perú.

Technologies and Skills



Work Experience

Jesuiz Design

Full Stack Developer & Graphic Designer

I implemented digital solutions in Web Development and Branding for businesses located in Peru, Puerto Rico and the USA. The services covered Visual Identity Design as well as Website Development, Ecommerce and Web Applications.

Clave Publicitaria 2022 - 2023

Wordpress Developer & Graphic Designer

As business manager, I managed to integrate new digital services to address a new unexplored market, where I executed Visual Identity Design and Website Development services, complementing the already established services of Printing, Gigantography and Merchandising.

Geotop 2021 - 2021

Wordpress Developer & Graphic Designer

I designed all the company's audiovisual material for digital and physical environments. I developed a new Website with Wordpress and optimized all the company's other websites. I managed all the company's graphic design, as well as the edition and transmission of the monthly Webinars.

Techno Global 2018 - 2021

Graphic Designer & Supervisor

I carried out designer activities related mainly to Social Media, Advertising, Printing and Gigantography. After 6 months I led the activities as store supervisor with 3 people in charge.

Education



Courses

EF Standard English Test: B2 Upper Intermediate EF SET Score: 59/100	2023	REST API course with PHP and MySQL Udemy	2023	Logical Thinking Course: Algorithms and Flowcharts Platzi	2023
PHP course with Laravel Platzi	2023	Introduction to PHP Frameworks Course	2023	REST API with PHP course Platzi	2023
Installation, Fundamentals and Operators of PHP Platzi	2023	Basic Computer and Informatics Course	2023		